'Bi?
[BEA] I'll wait for you outside.
- [BLOWS LAND]
- [COP GRUNTING]
[CALOY] I knew you couldn't
stay away from me.
We have a lot of work to do.
Happy birthday to me.
[PRECIOUS OVER PHONE]
It's a bit sad.
I don't think anyone
remembered my birthday.
I did! I remembered it's today!
Can I take you out to dinner later?
You can.
Bye.
I've fallen in love with Precious.
But I promise, at the right time,
I'll tell her everything.
[BILLY] You know what, dude?
I didn't expect Auntie Pres
to find love again
after Uncle Rico died
right on their wedding day.
I have always admired her
for being so cheerful
despite all our problems.
It's true.
True love transforms you.
It makes you whole.
It's a different sense of happiness
when someone loves you.
And when you love someone too.
Listen, Precious…
Sorry this is so last-minute.
What?
- She said yes.
- Okay?
- Yay!
- She's coming here.
Do you know who Auntie Pres is dating?
[LYDIA] It's Sir Eric.
Your aunt is dating Sir Eric.
[BILLY] Eric? As in, the same Sir Eric?
- Surprise!
- [PEOPLE CHEERING]
- [PRECIOUS LAUGHS] Billy!
[EVERYONE]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[PRECIOUS] Billy, you are
behind all this, aren't you?
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday
Happy birthday to you ♪
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE BEEPS]
[PRECIOUS GASPS]
Billy! Oh my God!
Are you okay?
You know him, Auntie?
[PRECIOUS] Uh…
Yes. That's Sir Eric.
I was planning to
tell you about him, Billy.
Billy, I can explain.
I didn't plan to hide it from your aunt--
You just won't leave us alone.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I only asked for one thing.
Billy--
[BILLY] Just leave.
Stay away from my family.
Billy, what's going on?
How could you be so selfish?
Seriously?
You even made a fool of the person
who raised us and cared for us
when that should have been you?!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
He's your father, Billy?
I didn't mean to fool anyone.
Precious…
Leave.
You're a liar!
- Precious…
- I said leave!
Never show your face here again! Leave!
Get out!
Are you okay?
Billy…
Dude…
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING] Billy, I'm sorry.
- I didn't know.
- Auntie Pres…
I really didn't know.
[SOBS, SNIFFLES]
I'm sorry too, that you
got dragged into this.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry that my father
is a liar. [SNIFFLES]
I was planning to tell you that
we've been going out.
I didn't know that the guy
who was nice to me and Oliver
was a huge liar.
[SNIFFLES]
He deceived me, Billy. He deceived us.
He humiliated us in front of everyone!
[SNIFFLES]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Auntie, you have nothing
to be ashamed of, okay?
You are not at fault.
If I could only choose our father,
I would've done it.
[SNIFFLES]
Forget about him.
Right. You're right, Billy.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[JORDAN] Auntie Pres? Billy?
Are you all right?
We'll take care of everything, okay?
We'll tell the guests to go home.
Mm-hmm. Excuse us.
Let's go.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG BILLY] Please don't leave us, Dad!
Please!
[YOUNG BILLY CRYING]
Please! [SOBS]
Mommy, please--
Don't waste your tears on worthless men.
We don't need him.
We can live without him.
[SNIFFLES, SOBS]
Please hear me out.
I know I did you wrong,
but forgive me, dear!
Dear, let me explain--
That's not necessary.
We're fine now.
Just leave.
Dear, I'm begging you.
No, I am begging you.
Let this be the last time
we see each other.
What are you doing here?
Dear…
Let's talk. Please?
We already did. Wasn't that enough?
Dear, just please hear me out.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- I can--
- Don't drag us into your mess.
I can explain.
Dear, I've made a lot
of bad decisions in my life.
And I want to make them right this time.
If you do this again,
I will file a restraining order.
I don't want any trouble,
but if you drag me into this,
my company, and especially Oliver,
I'll find a way
to have your case in Canada reopened.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're tired of waiting on you, Enrico.
Don't test our patience!
I don't care anymore.
You want to beat me up?
Just kill me!
Are you stupid?
We can't kill you just yet.
You owe us a huge sum!
If you really can't pay
the money back, fine.
I'll get it from your daughter.
I saw her at the hospital.
Looks like she's loaded.
She can probably pay off your debt.
Don't drag my daughter into this!
- [ENRICO GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [PAINED GROANS]
If you dare go anywhere near my children,
- I'll kill you!
- [GROANS]
Do you understand?!
[WHIMPERS, GROANS IN PAIN]
- [ENRICO PANTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THUG GROANING]
[METAL GATE CREAKS SHUT]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Bea.
Criselda is being annoying again.
When are you going to pay the rent?
I'm telling you,
that woman is testing my patience.
Uh, Ma…
[BEA] Don't worry about it, Ma.
I'll talk to Criselda.
I'll handle it.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES UNSETTLING]
[MUSIC FADES]
[OLIVER SINGING ON VIDEO CALL]
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
Happy birthday, Auntie!
Happy birthday!
Thank you, baby. Thank you too, Biboy.
Auntie, was your birthday celebration fun?
Mm-hmm. Yes.
But of course, I miss my baby.
Are you doing okay there?
If you don't feel well
or if there's a problem,
call us right away, okay?
What about you, Billy? Are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
Auntie Pres and I are just a bit tired.
Don't forget to put glucose tablets
and candies
in your pocket, okay?
I know you're doing
a lot of activities there,
but if you're not feeling well,
don't be shy to say it.
Yes, Billy.
All right then. I'll hang up now.
Thank you. Bye.
Good night.
Love you.
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you really okay?
What if Oliver sees the video,
Auntie Pres?
I can't believe Sir Er-- Enrico did that.
He even dragged Oliver's school into this.
I've sent an email to the school
and asked them to fire him
to make sure this won't happen again.
I'll also go there myself to check.
What if he keeps bothering you?
What if he becomes more desperate?
What if he tells Oliver the truth?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't want him to find out
from someone else.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[BAGS THUD]
Auntie, we won Best Team at the camp.
- Wow! That's great!
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, and Biboy's father apologized to me
when he picked him up earlier.
Oh. Really?
Yes, I was surprised.
I used to see him as feisty.
It turns out he's nice.
He even wished me luck on
my application to Kingsley.
I'm really excited to go to college.
Wait. Slow down, okay?
You still have to finish senior high.
Let's focus on that first.
Yes, I know, Auntie.
I'm just really excited
about going to college.
Remember what I told you?
The first thing I'll do
when I get to the US
is visit Papa's grave.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oliver,
let's talk.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know that I love you, right?
And that I'd do anything to protect you.
I also know…
that we made a promise
not to lie to each other.
But I broke that promise.
What do you mean?
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You want to study at Kingsley
because of our father, right?
The truth is, he's not buried abroad.
It's not true that he's dead.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Our father is still alive, Oliver.
He's alive?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I didn't tell you because
he abandoned us,
and I didn't want you to get hurt.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Auntie Pres and I love you so much.
Especially me. Right?
And I would do anything to protect you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Our father went to Canada.
Then,
he scammed a lot of people
and was sent to jail.
But now, he's back here
in the Philippines.
Where is he?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know Sir Eric,
the guy you met at school?
He's our father.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
But that's not his real name.
[MUSIC BECOMES SOMBER]
[BILLY] He lied to you and Auntie Pres.
But that won't happen again.
He won't get near you
and fool us ever again.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
I know this is confusing
and hard to understand.
It's hard to accept.
But--
I want to talk to him.
I don't want you to get hurt.
If you're really protecting me
and you don't want me to get hurt,
why did you lie to me?
And just because you're mad at him,
you want me to lose a father?!
I don't get it, Billy!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CRYING, MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY]
[JORDAN] Your sister
loves you so much.
Of course you would side with Billy.
I'm not siding with anyone.
Bro Dude, didn't you say
your father left you too?
If he came back,
wouldn't you want to talk to him?
I deeply regret what I did to
my children and to my wife.
Am I wrong?
We're the same.
I still can't forgive my dad either.
You've got some nerve, coming here!
Billy.
Oliver knows the truth.
I also told the school
about your real identity,
so you can no longer work there.
And you don't have a family
anymore either.
Why does he treat us this way?
What are we to him?
Trash?
Just trash.